Hello friends, Namaskar, I am your
friend Mr. Kayam Singh. I am
very happy to tell you that we are going to give you a very
important information,
as you must have understood what we are going to
give you,
as you must have seen the title thumbnail, by
looking at the title thumbnail you must have
understood what we are going to tell you, so
without any delay let's
take you to the video,
what kind of information is there, so first of all the
information that we are going to give you is that it is very
important for you to get health insurance, no matter who the person is,
considering your age, it is very important for all of you to get health
insurance
because health insurance is a very
necessary thing because someone or the
other is always short of money and
looking at the time, we have
also seen that someone or the
other definitely suffers from some kind of illness or the other, so
when there is an illness,
if you get health insurance, then
we want to tell you in a little detail about what benefits you get from it,
see if you have got health
insurance  And when you get health insurance,
what are the things you need to keep in mind while getting health insurance?
See, nowadays fraud is happening in many ways,
so you have to avoid fraud and
also do the proper work. So whenever you get health
insurance, you
must investigate the proper company. Don't fall into the hands of some fraudster
because fraud is very common these days.
You thought that we will get
health insurance for profit, but it does
not benefit you, there you end up incurring
loss. So you have to avoid loss
and also benefit from it because
all of us, whether normal or high level,
health insurance is very important
because no one can trust the body, when what
problem may arise,
what problem can arise, so at that time
if we do not have money or have it, then
how can it be dealt with? Look, the
information we gave you, first of all you have to get health
insurance and how to get it done,
definitely investigate it.
If you go to Vicholiya and find out that he told you some other
plan and you understood that it was okay,
but there many times people  If you get cheated,
you have to check the website as well.
You have to search thoroughly. This
is not a fraud company with which we
can get our health insurance. You should get
health insurance only if you have faith from within.
See what are the benefits of health insurance.
If we get health insurance, then
look at the health insurance, your premium amount is set according to the amount you get, 5 lakh, 8 lakh, 1.5 lakh, 10
lakh. And
you have to pay that premium amount in one go. If you buy any health
insurance company, then the first thing
you have to pay is which plan you are
taking and talk to them about
which diseases this health
insurance is covering for you. It is
very important to get this information because
when you get health insurance, you have to
investigate thoroughly about
which diseases are included in it,
which can benefit you.
See, there are many diseases inside the body
and no one knows which disease will come when.
So keeping all these things in
mind, when you get health
insurance, at that time, you should be completely careful.  We will
investigate, first of all when you have got health
insurance done and you have selected the plan, then along with that I will give
you one more information,
that information is that at the
time because if you have not done this then
you must have seen that the elephant's teeth are one thing for eating
and another for showing,
so you should not get trapped in these cycles, you have to get
health insurance done after proper investigation and while keeping the policy in mind,
you have to pay attention to these things
that what all is included in the policy that we are taking,
you have to do it in the same way, if you have
taken a policy of suppose 5 lakh rupees, then
which diseases are included in it, which we can take benefit from
if we face any problem in future, in the same
way,
what all is included in it and
see the things, if you have taken a policy of 5 lakh rupees at the same place, then
your premium amount will increase a bit,
if you have taken a policy of 10 lakh rupees at the same place, then
your premium amount will
increase in that too, yes the most important information is also
that if you have taken a policy and with it
you have taken a family insurance  Which people can be added as a member
and how many people can be added,
we will tell you that too, see,
you can get the option to add a member on a policy,
but
your premium
amount will increase in that, but the policy that will
remain, like suppose that you
took a policy of 10 lakhs, then when you took a policy of 10 lakhs,
suppose the
policy premium amount was 000, if
we add one more member in it, then some
amount of yours will definitely increase according to the age,
so keeping these things in mind,
you have to buy the policy, okay, and
this thing must be kept in mind that
which risk cover do we get in it and from when,
because if you do not get information about these things, then it is
possible that you and your
family may get cheated,
because recently I had received some
information, so I thought that for this
we should make some videos
so that people get some awareness about it
and in this way they
invest their money wisely, so see,
everyone knows how to earn money, but after earning money
If you are guided in the right place, then
that is the most important thing. No
one lags behind in earning money. Everyone earns money,
but not everyone knows how to use the money in the right place.
But what we are telling you is
information related to health insurance. There was a
person in our neighborhood who got
health insurance, but he got it done through a
middleman, through an agent, and
an incident happened with him.
When he got it done, the person who did his health
insurance, the
middleman, told him that everything is included in it.
Once, when he was returning from his job, he met with an
accident and
after the accident, he got hospitalized, the
expenses incurred in it were approximately Rs. 3 to 4 lakhs. The
insurance he had taken was for Rs. 6 lakhs,
but it was going against the policy
because the policy given by the middleman had been explained
something different and something different was
explained to him, so that was not included in it. In this
way, his  There was a loss and in this
way there was a loss, so we thought that
we should tell all of you people, if
you liked this video of ours, if you
got some information, then like this video as much as possible
and tell me by commenting
what we have missed in it,
what mistake we have made, what other things
should have been told which we missed in telling you
and in this way if you liked the video then
definitely like and subscribe the video so that we keep
bringing new videos like this among all of you
and keep giving new information to all of you,
because if you have all the information
then you will
not be able to get cheated anywhere because nowadays
a lot of scams are happening in some way or the other,
so to avoid scams, the only
option is that it is most important to have maximum information, whether
you are in it or not, it is
very important to have information, so without delay
watch this video, like,
subscribe and share your information,
Jai
Hind